<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

	<!-- Wood ARC upgrades -->
	<VQE_InstallWoodFiredGenetron>install wood-fired ARC core</VQE_InstallWoodFiredGenetron>
	<VQE_InstallWoodFiredGenetronDesc>Install wood-fueled furnaces that greatly improve the power output of the ARC core, but will change the generator to require wood to operate.</VQE_InstallWoodFiredGenetronDesc>
	<VQE_InstallWoodFiredGenetronDescExpanded>\n\nARC needs to operate uninterrupted for {0} (time at the moment: {1})</VQE_InstallWoodFiredGenetronDescExpanded>
	
	<VQE_InstallWoodFueledGenetron>install automated stoker</VQE_InstallWoodFueledGenetron>
	<VQE_InstallWoodFueledGenetronDesc>Install an automated system for feeding the fuel, keeping the furnace at optimal output with less frequent fueling.</VQE_InstallWoodFueledGenetronDesc>
	<VQE_InstallWoodFueledGenetronDescExpanded>\n\nARC needs to burn {0} fuel (fuel burned at the moment: {1})</VQE_InstallWoodFueledGenetronDescExpanded>
		
	<VQE_InstallWoodPoweredGenetron>install energy circulators</VQE_InstallWoodPoweredGenetron>
	<VQE_InstallWoodPoweredGenetronDesc>Install energy circulators that redirect excess heat back into the ARC core, amplifying power output with only a slight rise in fuel consumption.</VQE_InstallWoodPoweredGenetronDesc>
	<VQE_InstallWoodPoweredGenetronDescExpanded>\n\nARC needs to burn {0} fuel (fuel burned at the moment: {1})</VQE_InstallWoodPoweredGenetronDescExpanded>
	
	<VQE_InstallWoodBlastingGenetron>install adjustable burn cylinders</VQE_InstallWoodBlastingGenetron>
	<VQE_InstallWoodBlastingGenetronDesc>Install large, adjustable internal cylinders that allow altering the burn rate of the core, adjusting the power generated to fit the needs of the colony.</VQE_InstallWoodBlastingGenetronDesc>
	<VQE_InstallWoodBlastingGenetronDescExpanded>\n\nARC needs to operate uninterrupted for {0} (time at the moment: {1})</VQE_InstallWoodBlastingGenetronDescExpanded>
	
	<!-- Chemfuel ARC upgrades -->
	<VQE_InstallChemfuelPoweredGenetron>install chemfuel-powered ARC core</VQE_InstallChemfuelPoweredGenetron>
	<VQE_InstallChemfuelPoweredGenetronDesc>Install a set of chemfuel-operated engines that power up the ARC core, providing large quantities of energy by burning chemfuel. The engines will need regular maintenance, and if they break down, will require ARC components to be replaced.</VQE_InstallChemfuelPoweredGenetronDesc>
	<VQE_InstallChemfuelPoweredGenetronDescExpanded>\n\nARC needs to operate at 200% using ARC tuning uninterrupted for {0} days. (time at the moment: {1})</VQE_InstallChemfuelPoweredGenetronDescExpanded>
	<VQE_InstallChemfuelPoweredGenetronDescNoResearch>\n\nRequires Biofuel refining research to be completed.</VQE_InstallChemfuelPoweredGenetronDescNoResearch>
	
	<VQE_InstallChemfuelBoostedGenetron>install hyperburn chamber</VQE_InstallChemfuelBoostedGenetron>
	<VQE_InstallChemfuelBoostedGenetronDesc>Install a hyperburn chamber to superheat the combustion process and extract maximum energy from each unit of fuel.</VQE_InstallChemfuelBoostedGenetronDesc>
	<VQE_InstallChemfuelBoostedGenetronDescExpanded>\n\nARC overdrive needs to be active for {0} days. (time at the moment: {1})</VQE_InstallChemfuelBoostedGenetronDescExpanded>
	
	<VQE_InstallChemfuelChargedGenetron>install adaptive fuel modulator</VQE_InstallChemfuelChargedGenetron>
	<VQE_InstallChemfuelChargedGenetronDesc>Install an adaptive fuel modulator to adjust fuel flow dynamically, matching power demands and optimizing fuel usage. This ensures extended runtime and peak efficiency without sacrificing energy output.</VQE_InstallChemfuelChargedGenetronDesc>
	<VQE_InstallChemfuelChargedGenetronDescExpanded>\n\nPower surge needs to be activated {0} times. (activations at the moment: {1})</VQE_InstallChemfuelChargedGenetronDescExpanded>
	
	<VQE_InstallChemfuelFortifiedGenetron>install ignition stabilizer</VQE_InstallChemfuelFortifiedGenetron>
	<VQE_InstallChemfuelFortifiedGenetronDesc>Install an ignition stabilizer gizmo to ensure consistent and steady combustion, maintaining optimal power output and reducing fluctuations in fuel consumption. This upgrade enhances the generator's reliability and fuel efficiency. The stabilizer can be calibrated to permanently improve the power output.</VQE_InstallChemfuelFortifiedGenetronDesc>
	<VQE_InstallChemfuelFortifiedGenetronDescExpanded>\n\nARC needs to burn {0} fuel (fuel burned at the moment: {1})</VQE_InstallChemfuelFortifiedGenetronDescExpanded>
	
	<!-- Geothermal ARC upgrades -->
	
	<VQE_InstallGeothermalGenetron>install geothermal ARC core</VQE_InstallGeothermalGenetron>
	<VQE_InstallGeothermalGenetronDesc>Exchange the ARC core to utilise exclusively the steam energy produced by the geothermal vent. Doing so will decrease the power output significantly, but will also remove any fuel need completely. Geothermal ARC core will require regular maintenance, but can be maintained by everyone and not just the ARC specialists.</VQE_InstallGeothermalGenetronDesc>
	<VQE_InstallGeothermalGenetronDescNoResearch>\n\nRequires Geothermal power research to be completed.</VQE_InstallGeothermalGenetronDescNoResearch>
	<VQE_InstallGeothermalGenetronDescNoStudied>\n\nA colonist needs to study an ancient geothermal ARC somewhere in the world.</VQE_InstallGeothermalGenetronDescNoStudied>
	
	<VQE_InstallSteamPoweredGenetron>install vent booster</VQE_InstallSteamPoweredGenetron>
	<VQE_InstallSteamPoweredGenetronDesc>Install a thermal vent booster to enhance steam flow from geothermal vents, boosting the ARC’s power output during peak energy demands. This upgrade ensures higher efficiency and performance when needed most.</VQE_InstallSteamPoweredGenetronDesc>
	<VQE_InstallSteamPoweredGenetronDescExpanded>\n\nARC needs to operate uninterrupted for {0} (time at the moment: {1})</VQE_InstallSteamPoweredGenetronDescExpanded>
	
	<VQE_InstallThermalVentGenetron>install pressure surge protectors</VQE_InstallThermalVentGenetron>
	<VQE_InstallThermalVentGenetronDesc>Install a set of pressure surge protectors that will prevent the ARC from ever reaching a critical breaking point, while also increasing the power output.</VQE_InstallThermalVentGenetronDesc>
	<VQE_InstallThermalVentGenetronDescExpanded>\n\nSteam boost needs to be activated {0} times. (activations at the moment: {1})</VQE_InstallThermalVentGenetronDescExpanded>
	
	<VQE_InstallHeatPoweredGenetron>install flow regulators</VQE_InstallHeatPoweredGenetron>
	<VQE_InstallHeatPoweredGenetronDesc>Install a number of internal steam flow regulators that balance steam intake to ensure consistent performance, reducing wear and tear on the generator's components. Flow regulators allow the generator to operate even during a solar flare.</VQE_InstallHeatPoweredGenetronDesc>
	<VQE_InstallHeatPoweredGenetronDescExpanded>\n\nARC needs to operate uninterrupted for {0} (time at the moment: {1})</VQE_InstallHeatPoweredGenetronDescExpanded>
	
	<!-- Nuclear ARC upgrades -->
	
	<VQE_InstallUraniumPoweredGenetron>install uranium-powered ARC core</VQE_InstallUraniumPoweredGenetron>
	<VQE_InstallUraniumPoweredGenetronDesc>Install a large nuclear reactor in place of the old ARC core, utilising uranium to generate huge amounts of energy. The ARC will no longer be able to operate without fuel, and will shut down if it ever runs out of uranium. Maintenance and uranium supply will become essential in preventing devastating consequences.</VQE_InstallUraniumPoweredGenetronDesc>
	<VQE_InstallUraniumPoweredGenetronDescNoResearch>\n\nRequires Starship reactor research to be completed.</VQE_InstallUraniumPoweredGenetronDescNoResearch>
	<VQE_InstallUraniumPoweredGenetronDescNoStudied>\n\nA colonist needs to study a nuclear ARC husk somewhere in the world.</VQE_InstallUraniumPoweredGenetronDescNoStudied>
	
	<VQE_InstallNuclearGenetron>install uranium enrichment chamber</VQE_InstallNuclearGenetron>
	<VQE_InstallNuclearGenetronDesc>Install a chamber that allows you to slow down the decay rate of uranium, allowing it to generate power for a longer time.</VQE_InstallNuclearGenetronDesc>
	<VQE_InstallNuclearGenetronDescExpanded>\n\nUranium-powered ARC needs to be restarted. To do that, it needs to burn all uranium and shut down due to lack of fuel.</VQE_InstallNuclearGenetronDescExpanded>
	
	<VQE_InstallIsotopicGenetron>install radiation shielding</VQE_InstallIsotopicGenetron>
	<VQE_InstallIsotopicGenetronDesc>Install advanced shielding to reduce radiation exposure in nearby areas, making it safer for colonists when the reactor operates in unsafe mode.</VQE_InstallIsotopicGenetronDesc>
	<VQE_InstallIsotopicGenetronDescExpanded>\n\nARC needs to burn {0} uranium (uranium burned at the moment: {1})</VQE_InstallIsotopicGenetronDescExpanded>
	
	<VQE_InstallAtomicGenetron>install emergency shut-off systems</VQE_InstallAtomicGenetron>
	<VQE_InstallAtomicGenetronDesc>Install a system that instantly shuts down the reactor in dangerous situations, avoiding catastrophic failures and giving time for repairs. Additional safety mechanisms also allow anyone to maintain the atomic ARC, not just those who studied the ancient variants.</VQE_InstallAtomicGenetronDesc>
	<VQE_InstallAtomicGenetronDescExpanded>\n\nARC needs to operate uninterrupted in hazard mode for {0} (time at the moment: {1})</VQE_InstallAtomicGenetronDescExpanded>
	
	<!-- Downgrade ARC -->
	
	<VQE_DowngradeGenetron>Downgrade to {0}</VQE_DowngradeGenetron>
	<VQE_DowngradeGenetronDesc>Downgrade the ARC to an earlier stage of construction.</VQE_DowngradeGenetronDesc>
	<VQE_DowngradeGenetronDialog>Warning, this will downgrade the ARC to {0}. All materials used to upgrade it to the current stage will be lost. Are you sure you want to proceed?</VQE_DowngradeGenetronDialog>
	<VQE_DowngradeGenetronMeltdown>It's not possible to downgrade the ARC during a meltdown.</VQE_DowngradeGenetronMeltdown>
	
	<!-- Reactor abilities -->
	<VQE_GenetronOverdrive>ARC overdrive</VQE_GenetronOverdrive>
	<VQE_GenetronOverdriveDesc>Put the ARC in a temporary {0} overdrive mode. It will rapidly burn through fuel, generating significantly more energy. If at any point during the overdrive the fuel runs out, the generator will break down and require refurbishing with ARC components.</VQE_GenetronOverdriveDesc>
	<VQE_GenetronOverdriveDescExtended>\n\nOverdrive has a {0} cooldown. It will be ready again in {1}</VQE_GenetronOverdriveDescExtended>
	
	<VQE_GenetronTuning>ARC tuning</VQE_GenetronTuning>
	<VQE_GenetronTuningDesc>Alter the fuel consumption to increase or decrease the power generated by the ARC.</VQE_GenetronTuningDesc>
	<VQE_GenetronTuningSet>set ARC output to: {0}%</VQE_GenetronTuningSet>
	<VQE_GenetronTuningProjected>Projected power output: {0} Wd</VQE_GenetronTuningProjected>
	<VQE_FuelConsumptionProjected>Projected fuel burn rate: {0} per day</VQE_FuelConsumptionProjected>
	
	<VQE_GenetronFineTuning>ARC fine-tuning</VQE_GenetronFineTuning>
	<VQE_GenetronFineTuningDesc>Alter the fuel consumption to increase or decrease the power generated by the ARC, and adjust generator maintenance wear to boost the power output.</VQE_GenetronFineTuningDesc>
	<VQE_SetGenetronWear>set ARC wear to: {0}%</VQE_SetGenetronWear>
	
	<VQE_PowerSurge>power surge</VQE_PowerSurge>
	<VQE_PowerSurgeDesc>Instantly vaporize half of the remaining fuel in the ARC to create a surge of power, refilling the batteries at the cost of a significant 25% maintenance reduction of the ARC. Power surge will temporarily disable nearby electronics.</VQE_PowerSurgeDesc>
	<VQE_PowerSurgeDescExtended>\n\nPower Surge has a {0} cooldown. It will be ready again in {1}</VQE_PowerSurgeDescExtended>
	<VQE_PowerSurgeDescNoMaintenance>Power surge cannot be activated: ARC maintenance is too low (below 30%).</VQE_PowerSurgeDescNoMaintenance>
	
	<VQE_CalibrateEfficiency>calibrate efficiency</VQE_CalibrateEfficiency>
	<VQE_CalibrateEfficiencyDesc>Set the ARC into a low-power mode to calibrate its efficiency. While the fuel consumption will not change in the low-power mode, upon completion of the calibration, the power output will permanently increase by 1%.</VQE_CalibrateEfficiencyDesc>
	<VQE_CalibrateEfficiencyDescExtended>\n\nThe efficiency calibration has a {0} cooldown. It will be ready again in {1}</VQE_CalibrateEfficiencyDescExtended>
	
	<VQE_GenetronSteamTuning>pressure tuning</VQE_GenetronSteamTuning>
	<VQE_GenetronSteamTuningDesc>Alter the pressure of the ARC, affecting the wear and tear of components and the power output.</VQE_GenetronSteamTuningDesc>
	<VQE_GenetronPressureLabel>ARC pressure</VQE_GenetronPressureLabel>
	<VQE_GenetronSteamTuningMaintenance>set maintenance loss per day to: {0}%</VQE_GenetronSteamTuningMaintenance>
	
	<VQE_SteamBoost>steam boost</VQE_SteamBoost>
	<VQE_SteamBoostDesc>Temporarily enhance the steam flow by activating internal steam pumps, increasing the power output of the ARC for 5 days. The vent boosters will need to cool down for a period of time, preventing them from being used again until the temperature is optimal again.</VQE_SteamBoostDesc>
	<VQE_SteamBoostDescExtended>\n\nSteam boost has a {0} cooldown. It will be ready again in {1}</VQE_SteamBoostDescExtended>
	
	<VQE_CalibrateComponents>calibrate components</VQE_CalibrateComponents>
	<VQE_CalibrateComponentsDesc>Force a soft breakdown of the ARC, requiring parts of the core to be refurbished, in order to upgrade the internal workings of the core and improve the longevity of the components by 10%.</VQE_CalibrateComponentsDesc>
	<VQE_CalibrateComponentsDescExtended>\n\nCalibrate components has a {0} cooldown. It will be ready again in {1}</VQE_CalibrateComponentsDescExtended>
	
	<VQE_RestartGenetron>restart ARC</VQE_RestartGenetron>
	<VQE_RestartGenetronDesc>Jumpstart the nuclear ARC that has shut down due to lack of uranium. This restart can only be done if the ARC is filled with at least {0} uranium.</VQE_RestartGenetronDesc>
	<VQE_RestartGenetronDescExtended>\n\nThere isn't enough uranium in this reactor to restart it.</VQE_RestartGenetronDescExtended>
	<VQE_RestartGenetronDescNotNeeded>\n\nGenetron is running normally at the moment and doesn't require a restart.</VQE_RestartGenetronDescNotNeeded>
	
	<VQE_CalibrateFuelRods>calibrate fuel rods</VQE_CalibrateFuelRods>
	<VQE_CalibrateFuelRodsDesc>Temporarily shut down the reactor to calibrate the fuel consumption, allowing each unit of uranium to provide power for a longer time. Each calibration of fuel rods will reduce the fuel consumption rate by 10% of the remaining value.</VQE_CalibrateFuelRodsDesc>
	<VQE_CalibrateFuelRodsDescExtended>\n\nCalibrate fuel rods has a {0} cooldown. It will be ready again in {1}</VQE_CalibrateFuelRodsDescExtended>
	
	<VQE_SafeMode>safe mode</VQE_SafeMode>
	<VQE_SafeModeDesc>The ARC operates in safe mode. Burning uranium affects the maintenance of the ARC core, but no radiation is leaking from it. Activating this ability will change the ARC to operate in hazard mode.</VQE_SafeModeDesc>
	<VQE_HazardMode>hazard mode</VQE_HazardMode>
	<VQE_HazardModeDesc>The ARC operates in hazard mode. Burning uranium emits an unhealthy amount of radiation in radius, generating toxic buildup to everyone caught in it without toxic-resistant gear. The radius depends on the amount of uranium in the ARC. Maintenance of the ARC does not decrease. Activating this ability will change the ARC to operate in safe mode.</VQE_HazardModeDesc>
	<VQE_SafeModeInfo>Operating in safe mode.</VQE_SafeModeInfo>
	<VQE_HazardModeInfo>Operating in hazard mode.</VQE_HazardModeInfo>
	
	<VQE_EmergencyShutDown>emergency shut-down</VQE_EmergencyShutDown>
	<VQE_EmergencyShutDownDesc>Shut down the ARC. It will stop burning uranium, thus stopping the maintenance loss. It will also stop generating power until restart procedures are initiated.</VQE_EmergencyShutDownDesc>
	<VQE_EmergencyShutDownDescExtended>\n\nReactor is off now.</VQE_EmergencyShutDownDescExtended>
	
	<!-- Alerts -->
	
	<VQE_Alert_LowMaintenance>ARC maintenance low</VQE_Alert_LowMaintenance>
	<VQE_Alert_LowMaintenance_Desc>ARC requires maintenance. If no maintenance is performed, the ARC will critically break down.</VQE_Alert_LowMaintenance_Desc>
	<VQE_Alert_CriticalMaintenance>ARC maintenance critical</VQE_Alert_CriticalMaintenance>
	<VQE_Alert_CriticalMaintenance_Desc>ARC requires urgent maintenance. If no maintenance is performed, the ARC will critically break down.</VQE_Alert_CriticalMaintenance_Desc>
	<VQE_Alert_LowUranium>ARC low on uranium</VQE_Alert_LowUranium>
	<VQE_Alert_LowUranium_Desc>ARC is about to run out of uranium. When it does, it will become disabled until the restart procedures are initiated.</VQE_Alert_LowUranium_Desc>
	
	<!-- General stuff -->
	<VQE_NeedsStudy>{0} did not study an ancient ARC.</VQE_NeedsStudy> 
	<VQE_NeedsStudyGeothermal>{0} did not study an ancient geothermal ARC.</VQE_NeedsStudyGeothermal> 
	<VQE_NeedsStudyNuclear>{0} did not study a nuclear ARC husk.</VQE_NeedsStudyNuclear>
	<VQE_NeedsStudyGeneric>This colonist can't repair critical breakdowns, as they did not study an ancient ARC</VQE_NeedsStudyGeneric>
	<VQE_Overdrive>Reactor overdrive</VQE_Overdrive>
	<VQE_CriticalBreakdown>Critical breakdown</VQE_CriticalBreakdown>
	<VQE_CurrentMaintenance>ARC maintenance: {0}</VQE_CurrentMaintenance>
	<VQE_LowPowerMode>Low power mode. Remaining time: {0}.</VQE_LowPowerMode>
	<VQE_ShutDownForCalibrations>Shut down for calibrations. Remaining time: {0}.</VQE_ShutDownForCalibrations>
	<VQE_FuelRateAtTheMoment>Current fuel burn rate: {0} per day</VQE_FuelRateAtTheMoment>
	<VQE_ReactorShutdown>Reactor shut down</VQE_ReactorShutdown>
	<VQE_SetTargetUraniumLevel>Set target uranium level</VQE_SetTargetUraniumLevel>
	<VQE_SetTargetUraniumLevelTo>Set target uranium level to {0}</VQE_SetTargetUraniumLevelTo>
	<VQE_SetTargetUraniumLevelDesc>Set desired uranium level in the ARC. Colonists will try to fill the ARC up to that level.</VQE_SetTargetUraniumLevelDesc>
	<VQE_NuclearPowerOutput>Power output: {0}W</VQE_NuclearPowerOutput>
	<VQE_NuclearFuelConsumption>Fuel consumption per day: {0}</VQE_NuclearFuelConsumption>
	<VQE_GenetronMaintenanceTooltip>ARC maintenance
ARC needs to be maintained by colonists. If maintenance reaches 0%, ARC will break down.</VQE_GenetronMaintenanceTooltip>
    <VQE_TraitorLabel>Traitor {PAWN_nameDef}!</VQE_TraitorLabel>
    <VQE_TraitorLetter>{PAWN_nameDef}, known for creating the ARC, has turned against the colony. {PAWN_pronoun} admits that they plan to sabotage the ARC, believing the colony’s reliance on a single source of power is a fatal mistake.\n\n{PAWN_nameDef} argues that trusting one machine with everyone’s survival is a path to disaster. Unable to change minds through reason, {PAWN_pronoun} chose to act instead.\n\nYou can choose to capture {PAWN_objective}, kill them or banish them. However, preventing the sabotage is the top priority. Do not let {PAWN_nameDef} get to the ARC.</VQE_TraitorLetter>
	<VQE_MaintenanceImpact>ARC Maintenance in map</VQE_MaintenanceImpact>
	<VQE_NoTechnology>Will not equip: Ideology prohibits</VQE_NoTechnology>
	<VQE_AbilityNeedsComponent>This ability needs to target an advanced component.</VQE_AbilityNeedsComponent>

	<!-- Ancient ARC study -->
	
	<VQE_StudyAncientGenetron>Study {0}</VQE_StudyAncientGenetron>
	<VQE_StudyAncientGenetronDesc>Study the {0} to find out how to construct an operational one in your colony.</VQE_StudyAncientGenetronDesc>
	<VQE_StudyAncientGenetronDescExtended>\n\nThis {0} has already been studied or is in the process of being studied.</VQE_StudyAncientGenetronDescExtended>
	<VQE_FactionBecameHostileTimed>You've stayed in the village too long. The people of {FACTION_name} are attacking!</VQE_FactionBecameHostileTimed>
	<VQE_ThingWithInventorName>{0}'s {1}</VQE_ThingWithInventorName>
	<VQE_HasStudied>{0} has thoroughly studied the {1}</VQE_HasStudied>
	<VQE_PawnAlreadyStudied>{0} has already studied this structure</VQE_PawnAlreadyStudied>
	
	<!-- Traitor letter -->
	
	<VQE_TraitorSchism>Traitor schism ({0})</VQE_TraitorSchism>
	<VQE_TraitorSchismDesc>The creator of the ARC has turned out to be a traitor: {0} has been spreading their beliefs, convincing others to embrace an ideology that rejects technology. They have formed a new ideology: {1}. They argue that dependence on the ARC is reckless and will doom the colony. Their growing following now views the ARC as a threat, and whispers of sabotage have begun to surface. Left unchecked, this movement could escalate into conflict, putting your colony’s survival at risk.\n\nFollowing colonists have adopted {1}: {2}\n\nFollowers of {1} will refuse to do research. They will be unhappy if equipped with industrial-tech level or higher apparel and weapons, and will target technological items in their tantrums. Their priority will be destroying the ARC generator, and they will dislike anyone who holds the knowledge how to construct one of them.\n\nYou can consider exiling these colonists, or converting them back to their previous ideology.</VQE_TraitorSchismDesc>

	<VQE_InventorJoinsDesc>The {PAWN_title} named {PAWN_nameDef} has emerged from a cryptosleep casket and is joining the colony.\n\n{PAWN_nameFull}, the brilliant mind behind the creation of the ARC generator, brings a wealth of knowledge and experience. Across this planet, {PAWN_nameDef} tirelessly developed countless ARC prototypes, though many succumbed to neglect or external catastrophes. Despite these setbacks, {PAWN_nameDef} possesses unparalleled expertise in constructing, repairing, maintaining, and upgrading all known ARC generator types, including the advanced nuclear and geothermal variants. Moreover, {PAWN_nameDef} can attempt to salvage critical ARC components from advanced components, a skill that could prove invaluable in building or enhancing your colony’s own ARC generator.</VQE_InventorJoinsDesc>
	
	<!-- Mod settings -->
	
	<VQEG_DisableNeedForSteamVent>Disable the need of a steam vent to build an ARC</VQEG_DisableNeedForSteamVent>
	<VQEG_DisableNeedForSteamVentTooltip>By default, you will need a steam vent present in the map to build your ARC. With this mod option active, you can build them anywhere. Useful for gravships, for example.</VQEG_DisableNeedForSteamVentTooltip>
	<VQEG_ARCTimersMultiplier>ARC upgrade timer multiplier (lower means faster)</VQEG_ARCTimersMultiplier>
	<VQEG_ARCTimersMultiplierTooltip>When upgrading the ARC, there are a series of time periods the player needs to respect before being allowed to do the upgrades (eg "the ARC needs to run for X days in this mode before being upgraded"). This setting will apply a multiplier to those periods. Bear in mind a lower number means things will go faster. A higher number will mean the ARC will take longer.</VQEG_ARCTimersMultiplierTooltip>
	<VQEG_ARCFuelMultiplier>ARC upgrade fuel multiplier (lower means less fuel needed)</VQEG_ARCFuelMultiplier>
	<VQEG_ARCFuelMultiplierTooltip>When upgrading the ARC, there are some times when the player needs to burn a given amount of fuel before being allowed to do the upgrades (eg "the ARC needs to burn X wood before being upgraded"). This setting will apply a multiplier to those amount. Bear in mind a lower number means less fuel is needed. A higher number will mean more fuel.</VQEG_ARCFuelMultiplierTooltip>
	<VQEG_ARCOutputMultiplier>ARC power output multiplier</VQEG_ARCOutputMultiplier>
	<VQEG_ARCOutputMultiplierTooltip>This will scale the amount of power produced by the ARC reactors.</VQEG_ARCOutputMultiplierTooltip>
	<VQEG_Reset>Reset</VQEG_Reset>
</LanguageData>